iro ha nioi he do chirinuru wo
色は匂へど散りぬるを
Even fragrant flowers eventually scatters away
waga yotare zo tsunenara
我が世たれぞ常なら
Who in our world remains intransient?
hakanaki hana to chiru nonara
儚き花と散るのなら
If we’re scattering with the transient flowers
hitotsu koko de sasagemashou
ひとつここで捧げましょう
Then let’s devote one offering right here
tsutau shirabe kogareru karada to
伝う旋律焦がれる 身体と
Conveying the melody with the body that I yearn for
kokoro furuwaseru no hageshiku
こころ震わせるの激しく
And the intensity of my heart’s trembling
mijikaki sadame yo moyase moyase to afurete
短き運命よ
Oh, my fleeting destiny, burn, burn and overflow
燃やせ燃やせと溢れて
iza tomoni tate kono koe to tomoni maiagare
いざ共に立て
Come, stand with me and dance with this song
この歌声とともに舞い上がれ
sakihokore otome!
咲き誇れ音女！
Bloom proudly, Otome!
hyakkaryouran sakeru omoi yo
百花繚乱 咲ける意志よ
With the will of a hundred flowers blooming in profusion
tsuyoku are otome! yamato kokoro
強く在れ音女！ ヤマト心
Be strong, Otome! Carrying the heart of Yamato
wan, tsuu, san, hai!
ワン、ツー、さん 、はいっ！
One, two, three, go!
sakimidare otome! gouka kenran kochou no yumeyo
咲き乱れ音女！ 豪華絢爛 胡蝶の夢よ
Bloom wildly, Otome! With the dream of a gorgeous butterfly
mai odore otome! haru no arashi no yo ni
舞い踊れ音女！ 春の嵐の様に
Dance and whirl, Otome! Just like the Spring storm
sasageshi mi ni tagireru chi wo rinto himeyo
捧げし 身に 滾れる 血を 凛と 秘めよ
Regally hide the hot-bloodedness behind your dedication
kazarite nase ryouran seyo kono hana wa otome
飾りて 成せ 繚乱 せよ この花は乙女
Adorn and bloom profusely, this flower is a Otome